http://www.offsetservices.co.uk/privacy-policy

+44 (0)1925 828 069 info@offsetservices.co.ukISO CertifiedISO 45001:2018ISO CertifiedISO 14001:2015ISO CertifiedISO 9001:2015
HomeOur ServicesLaser ScanningPhotogrammetryDigital TwinsSmartPanoramicTMHeritage/Reverse EngineeringAs-Built CAD ModelIndustry Case StudiesOil & Gas Case StudiesFPSO SurveyFPSO HelideckLNG TrainGas Production PlatformGas Field PlatformOffshore Complex BruneiMalaysian PlatformOil TerminalOffshore JacketSarawak PlatformProcess Plant Case StudiesPower StationAmines PlantChlorine PlantWhisky DistilleryGas TurbinePilot PlantWater Treatment PlantCivil Case StudiesHM TreasuryAgarta ParkNuclear Case StudiesNuclear Power PlantNuclear ResearchRail Case StudiesTrain & Rail Side AssetsCrewe StationAbout UsContact UsGet In Touch
HomeOur ServicesLaser ScanningPhotogrammetryDigital TwinsSmartPanoramicTMHeritage/Reverse EngineeringAs-Built CAD ModelIndustry Case StudiesOil & Gas Case StudiesFPSO SurveyFPSO HelideckLNG TrainGas Production PlatformGas Field PlatformOffshore Complex BruneiMalaysian PlatformOil TerminalOffshore JacketSarawak PlatformProcess Plant Case StudiesPower StationAmines PlantChlorine PlantWhisky DistilleryGas TurbinePilot PlantWater Treatment PlantCivil Case StudiesHM TreasuryAgarta ParkNuclear Case StudiesNuclear Power PlantNuclear ResearchRail Case StudiesTrain & Rail Side AssetsCrewe StationAbout UsContact UsGet In Touch
Skip to contentHomeOur ServicesLaser ScanningPhotogrammetryDigital TwinsSmartPanoramicTMHeritage/Reverse EngineeringAs-Built CAD ModelIndustry Case StudiesOil & Gas Case StudiesFPSO SurveyFPSO HelideckLNG TrainGas Production PlatformGas Field PlatformOffshore Complex BruneiMalaysian PlatformOil TerminalOffshore JacketSarawak PlatformProcess Plant Case StudiesPower StationAmines PlantChlorine PlantWhisky DistilleryGas TurbinePilot PlantWater Treatment PlantCivil Case StudiesHM TreasuryAgarta ParkNuclear Case StudiesNuclear Power PlantNuclear ResearchRail Case StudiesTrain & Rail Side AssetsCrewe StationAbout UsContact UsGet In TouchHome Privacy Policy
Share
FacebookTwitterLinkedInEmail
Home Privacy Policy
Share
FacebookTwitterLinkedInEmail
February 18, 20201. Key detailsThis website privacy policy describes how Offset Services Limited protects and makes use of the information you give the company when you use this website.If you are asked to provide information when using this website, it will only be used in the ways described in this privacy policy.This policy is updated from time to time. The latest version is published on this page.This website privacy policy was updated on: 22nd May 2018.If you have any questions about this policy, please email info@offsetservices.co.uk.2. IntroductionWe gather and use certain information about individuals in order to provide products and services and to enable certain functions on this website.We also collect information to better understand how visitors use this website and to present timely, relevant information to them.3. What data we gatherWe may collect the following information:Name and job titleContact information including email addressDemographic information, such as postcode, preferences and interestsWebsite usage dataOther information relevant to client enquiriesOther information pertaining to special offers and surveys4. How we use this dataCollecting this data helps us understand what you are looking from the company, enabling us to deliver improved products and services.Specifically, we may use data:For our own internal recordsTo improve the products and services we provideTo contact you in response to a specific enquiryTo customise the website for youTo send you promotional emails about products, services, offers and other things we think might be relevant to you.To send you promotional mailings or to call you about products, services, offers and other things we think might be relevant to you.To contact you via email, telephone or mail for market research reasons.5. Cookies and how we use themWhat is a cookie? A cookie is a small file placed on your computer’s hard drive. It enables our website to identify your computer as you view different pages on our website.Cookies allow websites and applications to store your preferences in order to present content, options or functions that are specific to you. They also enable us to see information like how many people use the website and what pages they tend to visit.How we use cookies We may use cookies to:Analyse our web traffic using an analytics package. Aggregated usage data helps us improve the website structure, design, content and functions.Identify whether you are signed in to our website. A cookie allows us to check whether you are signed in to the site.Test content on our website. For example, 50% of our users might see one piece of content, the other 50% a different piece of content.Store information about your preferences. The website can then present you with information you will find more relevant and interesting.To recognise when you return to our website. We may show your relevant content, or provide functionality you used previously.Cookies do not provide us with access to your computer or any information about you, other than that which you choose to share with us.Controlling cookiesYou can use your web browser’s cookie settings to determine how our website uses cookies. If you do not want our website to store cookies on your computer or device, you should set your web browser to refuse cookies.However, please note that doing this may affect how our website functions. Some pages and services may become unavailable to you.Unless you have changed your browser to refuse cookies, our website will issue cookies when you visit it.To learn more about cookies and how they are used, visit All About Cookies.6. Controlling information about youWhen you fill in a form or provide your details on our website, you will see one or more tick boxes allowing you to:Opt-in to receive marketing communications from us by email, telephone, text message or post.Opt-in to receive marketing communications from our third-party partners by email, telephone, text message or post.If you have agreed that we can use your information for marketing purposes, you can change your mind easily, via one of these methods:Sign in to our website and change your opt-in settings.Send an email to info@offsetservices.co.uk.Write to us at: The Genesis Centre, Science Park South, Birchwood, Warrington, WA3 7BH.We will never lease, distribute or sell your personal information to third parties unless we have your permission or the law requires us to.Any personal information we hold about you is stored and processed under our data protection policy, in line with the Data Protection Act 1998.7. SecurityWe will always hold your information securely.To prevent unauthorised disclosure or access to your information, we have implemented strong physical and electronic security safeguards.We also follow stringent procedures to ensure we work with all personal data in line with the Data Protection Act 1998.8. Links from our siteOur website may contain links to other websites.Please note that we have no control of websites outside the offsetservices.co.uk domain. If you provide information to a website to which we link, we are not responsible for its protection and privacy.Always be wary when submitting data to websites. Read the site’s data protection and privacy policies fully. View our Case Studies View our GlossaryISO CertifiedTop
This site uses cookies to improve your experience. By continuing to use our site we will assume you agree to our Privacy PolicyI Agree
